

Abdel Chafii

Sr Global Support Services Representative

Contact

abdel.chafii@outlook.com

Barcelona (08014) Spain
(+34) 662118064

Linkedin

Skills

ADP HR systems

Data Integration: ADP HCM systems, Oracle, Workday, Successfactors.

Root Cause Analysis

Microsoft Dynamics CRM

Power BI reporting

Project management

Dynatrace Monitoring

Data Analysis

Sharepoint & Confluence

SAP - Basic

Microsoft Office - Excel

HTML & CSS - Basic

Technical/Soft skills and Adaptability

About me

Adviser/Influencer. With over 10 years in Support Services and IT, I possess advanced critical thinking, problem-solving and Soft skills, and a versatile background in data analysis, Access Management and Process Improvement. I am currently responsible of global support projects activities related to Celergo Product, In collaboration with Integration, Implementation, development and Security teams,

Quick learner with a strong ability to adapt to new tools and eager to acquire additional skills

Enthusiastic about blockchain and AI for their revolutionary potential in remodeling industries and unlocking unprecedented possibilities.

Experiences

ADP - October, 2023 - Present

Senior Global Service Support Representative at ADP

As SME of Celergo Product, I am serving as Escalation Point and assigned to address the RCA in collaboration with cross-functional teams

Collaborating with internal teams and stakeholders involved in the processing of Payroll/Integration in Production Environment - Go Live events.

Handover Documentation, SharePoint Administration and KB maintenance Transition to Service post approval monitoring and contributing to the overall effectiveness of service delivery

Sharing knowledge and Contributing in OBT Sessions.

ADP - March, 2021 - September 2023

Global Service Support Representative at ADP

Participating in CS projects: Service Model and Scope, SLA, Transition to Service, Monitoring and Reporting

Collaboration with DEV/Implementation teams: Call sessions, training and sharing documentation related to Support Model, New enhancements and Releases knowledge transfer

Collaborating closely with Integration team: Monitoring Live Client data integration errors, Reporting technical failures, SORs configuration/update

Internal Projects: SR queues Management and Support, Service Catalog, Power BI Reporting - Team performance, Escalations Process and KPIs

. . . .

Courses

ADP - Celergo Learning Path

ADP - Project Management course

Agile Scrum Master Certification Training

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure -Certified Foundations Associate - Udemy

Data Integration Fundamentals - Udemy

Oracle Data Integrator (ODI) 12c Developer Course

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials

Cybersecurity Essentials - Cisco Academy

Introduction to Packet Tracer - Cisco Academy

Cloud Computing - Google

Chat GPT courses - Udemy

NDG Linux Essentials - Cisco Academy Providing support to CAMs: Access Administration, Configuration, Integration failures investigation, Import and Export files errors, Mapping.

Additionally, providing Guidance, Analysis and reporting for decision support and Improvements

Computacenter - July, 2014 - July, 2020

T2 IT Support Analyst - Airbus

Focused on Providing Support to L1 Analysts, covering Escalations and High priority SRs for Airbus Account Admin users/Privileged contacts

Computacenter - April 2013 - July 2014 IT Support Analyst - Air Liquide

Multilingual IT Support for EN, SP, and FR speaker

Avis Budget Group - April, 2012 - October, 2012 Booking/Support Team Agent

Booking & Service Desk Support tasks

Education

Human Sciences Hassan II University - Casablanca 1998 - 2000 Human Science - Law

ISTA - OFPPT 2000 - 2002 Technicien Spécialisé en Restauration

Languages

English, French, Spanish, Catalan and Arabic